所以我们将再次替换一个
So once again we're going to replace the one
我们的测试的剩余部分，还有一个
remaining part of our test, that still has a
标准数据库。让我们摆脱我们的数据库
standard database. Let's actually get rid of our database.
只留下单独的insert语句。
That leaves us with this lonely insert statement. Once
再一次像其余的事情一样，我们将取代
again, like with everything else, we're going to replace that
内容解析器调用。当然我们
with a content resolver call. And of course we're
实际上不会插入表中。我们将
actually not going to be inserting the table. We're going
插入内容的URI，删掉Null。
inserting the content URI. Getting rid of the nulls.
当然这并不返回位置行ID。
Of course this doesn't return a location row ID.
这是对的。我们可以把它从URI里取出来，
That's alright. We can pull it from the URI. Using
使用contentURIs的helper函数,让插入留在那吧
the helper function from content URI's, we can leave
虽然这并不是必要的
that insert in there, although it's not necessary. And the
其他一切都应该差不多一样
rest of everything should pretty much be as it
我们不再在testprovider里使用数据库
always is. We're no longer using a database at all
完全使用内容提供者
within test provider, but entirely using the content provider.
运行我们的测试,看看他们是否仍然工作
Let's run our tests and see if they still work.
[BLANK_AUDIO]
全部通过。祝贺你,我们现在
And they all pass. Congratulations, we now
有一个功能完备的内容提供者
have a fully functioning content provider that can
他们可以插入和查询
both insert and query. But, of course,
当然还有其他你可能想使用内容提供者做的事
there are other things you might want to do
目前，我们不会
with the content provider. Now, we're not
使用它们
actually going to use any of these things
但是这真的很重要
in Sunshine. But it's really important to know.
所以,我建议你真正实现这些功能
So, I suggest you actually implement these functions.